But I think it's a great time to be
invested in stocks specifically. And I
think you should be very limited in your
cash position and you should be looking
to allocate whenever and wherever
possible cuz I think we are in an
incredible opportunity in the markets.
What's up everybody? It's LG here and
welcome to Milk Road Stocks, the daily
market show where things have been up
only since our launch and it doesn't
look like that's about to change. Today
is August 19th, 2026 recording on August
18th. The economy is strong. Inflation
isn't currently forcing the Fed's hand,
and AI demand is accelerating. Plus,
those companies are actually showing
real returns. Finally, for example,
Anthropics revenue has grown 300%
quarter over quarter and is projected to
climb another 2 to 4x 207. This is the
setup for the Everything Bull Market, a
term coined by our co-owner and market
analyst, Cal Reedhead, who has loaded up
his portfolio with companies set to bank
on the continuation of this incredible
market we've been in. and he's on the
show today to show us the macro data
that points to no rate hikes anytime
soon and dig into those profits I just
mentioned. All of his insight, his
trades, his calls are available in
Milkroad Pro alongside our four other
analysts. They have made some banger
calls this year. For example, Melvin,
his portfolio is up 40% since February.
So, if you'd put 10K into his moves,
you'd have over $4,000 in gains already.
Milk Road Pro is so good that we're
actually bringing up the price from $25
to $39 a month and $250 to $299
annually. But you, our loyal listeners,
you can still get the old pricing for
just another 6 days. You have until
August 25th to go pro for just 25 bucks
at the link below. And a reminder that
our podcast today is free and that it
wouldn't be possible without our
partners at SaberMoney, the stablecoin
payments platform built for Asia. Keep
an ear out for more information about
them later in the show. Kyle, listen. I
love doing these episodes where it's
just the two of us. Uh you always paint
a nice picture of what's going on, what
assets you like, and today I want to
hear about this theory, this thesis,
this idea that you've been proliferating
uh called the everything bull market.
Like what is that? [laughter]
>> Yeah, I've been uh I've been hammering
the everything bull market on Twitter a
lot uh over the last I don't know, maybe
two months or three months. Um for for
multiple reasons. Um the everything bull
market has a macro thesis to it. Um and
then it also has a technological
um integration or adoption thesis to it.
Um and when I say everything bull
market, it actually it's a little
misleading because it doesn't mean every
single thing is going to go up, which
you would think when I say that it's
everything that's involved in AI is
going to go up. So unfortunately for the
crypto listeners, uh you do not
participate in this everything bull
[laughter] market. uh but a lot of
things do this does touch most things uh
and to be honest at some point it will
actually pull in crypto along with it um
but there are certain companies that are
not going to participate in this the old
companies you know that that are not
really using AI and and and probably
won't um they will not be part of the
everything bull market but everything
from the infrastructure layer to even
the model layer which I think a lot of
people think is cooked um to the
application layer um and and the
application layer is very vast all of
them particip ipate in what I call the
everything bull market and it's backed
by an incredible goldilocks backdrop on
the macro side of things that is
enabling this. So I think those two
things um is what's powering the
everything bull market. I think it's a
great time to be invested in stocks
specifically and I think you should be
very limited in your cash position and
you should be looking to allocate
whenever and wherever possible because I
think we are in an incredible
opportunity in the markets. I think it's
a really hard thing for people to to
wrap their head around too, Kyle. And I
think this is why I was excited to do
this episode with you is that it's just
you have markets at all-time high,
right? And a lot of, you know, even
people on our show like you guys tell
us, our analysts that it's like, listen,
but we're just at the start of this
buildout, right? Like this is we're
totally shifting into a new type of
technology. A lot of companies are
completely changing their models. The
hyperscalers are used to do completely
different things than what they're doing
now. And I think that's just something
hard for people to to to grasp um that
things are going to continue to rip in
this setup. So I think that's, you know,
we'll talk a little bit more about that
today.
>> Well, and we'll talk about timing
because everything bull market doesn't
mean we don't have pullbacks. And
actually, when I first started screaming
about the everything bull market, it was
while we were going into this huge
pullback. And the reason I came up with
it was I did a bunch of research during
that time of why are we pulling back
here, right? This was in July. um well I
guess like mid mid June it started and I
said okay well is this the end of the
bull market or you know what's going on
and so I started looking into the macro
deeply which I already look at anyway
but I just wanted to recheck my numbers
was looking into what was happening in
terms of you know the adoption of AI and
where the ROI was with AI and that's
when I actually came out with this
everything bull market was at the the
peak bottom of this whole thing or at
least while we were going down and it
gave me the conviction to buy a bunch of
assets during that that pullback and so
there will still be pullbacks along the
way but I think this everything bull
market is what helps you to have that
conviction during those moments so do I
buy when we're at peak tops you know
sometimes but I prefer not to I prefer
to buy during fear which we just had and
it's this thesis that allowed me to do
that
>> yeah I like that so what I'd like to
learn Kyle you talked about goldilocks
between like basically
the stocks and the hypers scales and
basically the entire market and also
like what's happening in macro data. So,
I feel like that's a good place to start
to understand that. Um, we had a macro
channel for a long time. We still cover
it once a week. John writes a whole
write up about it. We have our uh Milk
Road macro index that our pro members
can look at every week that or every day
basically that kind of tracks all of
that stuff together, but I think it's
always helpful to dig into the numbers
individually, too.
>> Yeah. So, there's a few reasons why the
macro matters. one, obviously if macro
is is solid um and the economy is
booming and earnings is booming, then
typically that's a time when stocks are
doing quite well, right? But what you
really want to understand is when the
economy is booming and when earnings are
going through the roof, this is also a
time to be quite vigilant in your
investing because it tells you that
generally at some point you're going to
reach a top. The Fed is likely going to
raise rates or things are going to flip
and we're going to go down the other
way. And once we start to decelerate in
a good in a good market, that's when we
start to sell off, right? And so the the
the you know, easiest example of this
was 2021 2020 was an incredible bull
market. You know, we saw the the ISM
going through the roof. Earnings were
going through the roof. Like it was just
a crazy time. And then what happened is
whenever you have a lot of demand and
consumption, inflation starts to pick up
and uh you know you have well first you
have low unemployment, you have wage
growth growth which is growing um and
thus people have a bunch of money to
spend and so they spend everywhere.
Consumption is crazy. Inflation picks up
as a result of that and then the Fed
needs to raise rates. Now that's a big
problem if the Fed starts raising rates
because a lot of this infrastructure
buildout and what's going on in AI is
being financed. And so we want to make
sure rates remain or even go lower to
keep this bull market alive. Now what
we're seeing in capex is so big that you
know one hike or two hikes might not
even matter because the growth in AI uh
and the the growth in capex is so big
that it's surpassing you know what are
we at right now? I don't remember 3.2 or
3.5% whatever like it's it's it's bigger
than that. So it actually doesn't matter
that much. But if we you know bring
rates much higher um then at some point
it is going to impact things. Now what
I'm kind of trying to argue right now is
that the economy is in this kind of
goldilocks moment where what I have up
on the screen here is the ISM. The ISM
is above 56. This means that the economy
is absolutely booming. It's expanding.
This is a really really good sign for
the economy. Now generally when this
happens though you want to start
thinking about when is the top coming
because when the economy is expanding
and the economy is booming especially
when we look at earnings is also
expanding right generally what this
means is that we're going to be hiring a
ton wage growth is going to be
increasing consumption is is increasing
and thus um we're going to have to start
to raise rates because inflation should
go higher and I think that what's
happening though is that's not the case
today we are seeing currently an
expanding growing growing economy,
expanding and growing earnings, but we
are not seeing employment pick up like
crazy. We are not seeing jobs pick up
like crazy. We are not seeing wage
growth pick up like crazy. And thus
inflation is actually coming down rather
than going up. And that is the
Goldilocks moment. And I think not all
of it but some of it has to do with the
fact that the reason we are seeing
earnings growth pick up so much is
because we are seeing the integration
and the adoption of AI and soon AI
agents which is growing revenues without
growing the human account the human
count inside of companies. And thus
humans aren't necessarily making more.
They're not making a lot less either,
right? They're not like it's not like
we're losing a ton of jobs here because
of AI. We're just not hiring a ton at
the moment, which is great. Uh because
it means that companies can do well
without needing to hiring more and that
means the stock market can go much
higher without causing inflation to go
much higher. And that's the key part of
this all. So if you look at inflation
right now, here's the chart that shows,
you know, this is what happened back in
2022. Whole different world. This was a
supply chain issue. We don't have that
today. Um we had a spike in inflation
which was scaring the market a little
bit. Um earlier this year it went all
the way up to 4.2%. 2% and now it is on
its way down. This was because of oil.
This was because of the Iran war, right?
So basically nothing else spiked except
for uh energy and in and the the the
cost of oil um because obviously we
closed the straight of her and there was
a lot of issues there. That is becoming
less of an issue. It's not solved yet,
but becoming much less of an issue. And
thus we're seeing inflation come back
down. Now the Fed wants that 2%. We're
still at 3.4. So, we're not there yet,
but we are seeing a lot of the long-term
things that are slow and take a while to
come down like shelter um and energy.
These are starting to come down over
time slowly. So, meaning uh the cost of
homes and that are coming down. Uh and
that takes a while, but it's it's it's
kind of steady and continues its way
down. And so, I think we're going to
continue to see inflation make its way
down. Will it make its way to 2%? I'm
not sure. But based on this, as long as
we continue to come lower and don't
forget GA or not gas, but uh oil is
still quite high because we keep having
these like mixed fears. So, it still has
a long ways to come down. And if it
comes back down to like its 60s, I think
it's in the what is it the 80s right
now? We can check right now while we're
here. Oil is currently at 84. So, we've
got a long ways to go to come down. Um
and it can make its way down to in the
60s. Now, if that happens, that's going
to bring inflation down really big. And
I do think, you know, we've been in a a
down pattern since March. So, I think
that's going to make it back down into
the 60s at some point. Um, and uh, and
that's going to be the next driver of
bringing inflation lower closer to 2%. I
don't know if it actually gets to 2%,
but we want to see it get there. Now,
the other thing to keep in mind is the
Fed doesn't look at this metric, the
CPI. It looks at other metrics, whether
it's like true inflation or, you know, I
don't know which which one it looks at,
but it looks at more like real-time
data, which already shows much closer to
2% than what CPI shows here. This is
lagging data and honestly it's it's kind
of outdated. So if we think inflation is
going to continue to come down the other
thing we can look at is you know
generally you would see in a time when
the economy is expanding and earnings
are crashing you would see uh
unemployment uh would come down which it
is but it's still about 4%. It's nowhere
near where it was back here at like in
the 3% right. So, there's still many
months left of kind of unemployment kind
of staying as is or slowly beginning to
come down. Like, at some point, we
should be hiring a bunch more because
the economy is doing so well, but we're
not there today, which means there's
still a lot of time left in this market.
Um, and then if we look at non-farm
payrolls, it's doing the opposite. So,
we're actually seeing jobs um decrease,
right? Um, which is quite interesting.
And so, the the market is telling us
that something different is happening
here. generally um the opposite should
be happening and it's not and so the
market's telling us that I think AI is
the thing that's making a lot of these
earnings really pick up uh in terms of
the economy at the moment and so that's
why the market right now in Kelshi is
saying that you know I think I was on
the show was it last week or two weeks
and it was like a 60% chance they were
going to raise rates in September we're
now at a 71% chance that they are going
to keep it as is we're even starting to
price in a bit of a cut. We're at like
1.2%. Okay. Uh so I don't think that's
going to happen, but you know, we used
to think that they were going to raise
rates in September. Now it looks like
it's pretty much for sure that that is
not going to happen. And so that's the
Goldilocks moment in the setup for us.
That tells us, hey, it looks like stocks
can go higher for longer. Earnings can
go up for longer without the Fed having
to intervene, without inflation going
higher. If you're not a Pro member, what
the hell are you doing? On August 26th,
the price of Milk Road Pro is going up.
Monthly goes from 25 bucks to 39 and
annual goes from 250 to 299. And here's
why. Pro used to be a paid newsletter
with one portfolio attached. Now it's a
full platform. Five analysts running
real-time portfolios with every
position, every trade, and piece of
reasoning out in the open with live
notifications to keep you in the know.
And the results have been insane.
Melvin's portfolio launched in February
and it's up 41% since. If you put 10
grand behind his moves, then you'd be
sitting on more than four grand in
gains. 5 months of pro costs just 125
bucks over that same stretch. Is there a
better ROI on any investment right now?
If you join before midnight Eastern on
August 25th, you keep today's price for
as long as you're a member. After that,
it's gone for good. The link is in the
show notes. Mhm. [clears throat] And
that's that's that that number on Kelshi
and Poly market. It is consistent for
all the upcoming Fed sessions through to
January. It's like 65 to 75% of
maintaining the rate. So that's that's
not just for that's not just for next
month. It's for the next like quarter
beyond. Um so clearly the market is
starting to price that in.
>> There's a chance we get the rest of the
year without them raising rates now
which is pretty crazy because the market
had priced in a bunch. So that in itself
as the market continues to sort of
figure that out and we'll see what
happens in September when they give us
their their speech. Um but assuming they
don't raise rates and they even say look
we think the market's fine. We don't
need to touch it for the end of the
year. That's your reason where we can be
at all-time highs in terms of the stock
market and they can go much much much
higher.
>> Kyle, is AI going to create jobs?
Because I think we we've talked we
talked about this a year ago. We talked
about this for a long time is you were
basically describing this K-shaped
economy. We talked about it with Martin
earlier this week on the podcast as
well. Um that basically, you know,
you're showing us that unemployment
rate, which is actually going down. I
didn't realize that, but also that we
had a net negative last month in
non-farm uh payroll jobs as well. So,
what what do you think actually happens
here? Because I think that that's
largely the concern from also like a
moral standpoint that it's like, yes, we
want to buy these stocks. We want them
to go higher, but also does it mean that
nobody has jobs? Or do you think we'll
have more jobs?
>> I think we'll have more jobs. I think if
we're going to So I I I don't think that
this what I'm painting here, this
Goldilocks picture is going to last for
forever. It's lasting right now, right?
And because what I do think is going to
happen is the economy is going to
continue to expand. Where's that chart?
Earnings are going to continue to go up.
The economy is going to continue to
expand. Um but I think as a result of
that, companies will start hiring more
people. But I think what they'll hire is
people that are using AI. So, the reason
why I think we actually get more jobs
out of this than less jobs is because
companies are getting so profitable when
they use AI that they're going to want
to bring in more people that use AI to
bring in more profit because what's
happening here is just your profit per
employee is increasing, right? And so,
even, you know, I run two companies,
both of our companies have hired and
continue to hire people so long as they
use AI because if they use AI, we know
that we can generate more revenues from
them. And so I think that's the world
that we're going into right now is um
companies are just going to look for
more people that can use AI and it's
getting easier and easier to use AI
which is great as well. And so I think
as a result you're going to end up
hiring more people not less. It's funny
I was had a my family over. Uh my
family's from like a very small town so
they're not very AI uh at all but one of
my cousins was using AI and so we were
having this debate. My dad and a few
others thought okay well if AI is so
good everyone's just going to lose their
job. And I and I spent about a half hour
explaining to them, no, no, no. Look, if
you use AI, you become way more
efficient, which means more like
companies are going to want to hire you
even more, right? Because you can get
more done. You can make more money from
them. And that's the key thing that I
think the market is missing. Plus,
you're going to have a bunch of brand
new jobs that come out as a result of
this that we can't even think of. So, I
think um in the short to medium term,
more jobs are coming. I don't know what
happens when robotics come, but that's a
2029, 2030 story, and that's really
going to take a while to scale out. I'm
sure there'll be different jobs at that
point, but for now, I think we're in a
moment where AI is going to create more
jobs, better earnings, um, and push the
economy much further. Now, when that
happens though, as more jobs come, we,
you know, and the economy is doing so
well, we will consume more, and that
will potentially drive inflation higher.
The reason why I say potentially is
usually it always does drive inflation
higher. However, if we can get AI and
manufacturing and robotics to kick in,
it could drive the prices down for a lot
of things. And so maybe there's a world
where we can have employment really
good. Um, and the economy doing really
good, but inflation actually doesn't go
higher because the cost of goods is
actually going down because, you know,
renewables and energy is really kicked
in because we needed that for data
centers. Um, the ability to manufacture
is much faster than we've ever had
before. um you know the cost of you know
things goes down because you know AI
makes it way cheaper, our software goes
cheaper. Like I don't know when that
plays out. So I'm sure we'll probably
get inflation pickup before then but I
don't know. Let's see.
>> Kyle, what did your did your family
believe you? Did they agree with you
when you explained [laughter] all that
to them?
>> I think by the end of it, yes, cuz I
gave a lot of examples and really like
went into it, but it took a while,
that's for sure. There was a lot of
fight push back. this it's always good
to get it's always good to step out of
our um uh our little circle here and
hear what you know non-stock people want
to like think of the pro or think about
AI and and the everything bull market
>> the main thing that they were stuck on
was kids can cheat at their exams and I
was like here's the thing you got to
understand [laughter]
is it used to be like really good if you
ended up um you know like you had to
make a 10-page report on our example we
talked about was building a bridge Okay.
And I don't know why. So, let's say this
is an engineering class or whatever. And
I was like, "Okay, you write a 10-page
essay." And they were like, "Well, now
you can just get AI to write that
essay." I was like, "Sure, you can." But
now, instead of me handing in a 10-page
essay, I can hand in the the entire
engineering blueprint for what materials
I need, the exact architecture of this
of this bridge with all the specs, plus
a 3D rendering of this bridge, plus like
I can find all the companies that we
need to buy the materials and how long
it will take, and I can have a whole
plan, which you would only get from like
a full engineering company. Now, as a
grade 10 student, I could give you that
entire thing. So, I don't hand in TED
page essays anymore. I hand in a full 3D
video rendering with all the specs and
the engineering blah blah. And I was
like, that's the new way that you do uh
projects in school, right? Because AI
allows you to be more efficient. And
they were like, oh, dang. And so that's
when I got them to to spin their head
and go, "Okay, I see it now." So that's
you can apply that to employees, right?
That's how employees become more
efficient because someone you used to
need like, you know, it used to be very
costly to get all those things. Now, one
person can do all that stuff. So, it
makes one employee go a lot further.
>> I think that's a really good way to put
it. I'm going to use that next time I'm
having the argument that it's like it's
not it's not that they they're going to
be able to fasttrack their 10-page
report is that the assignment should no
longer be a 10-page report now that they
can do so much more. I like that. I
think that [laughter] that's that's
that's actually a really good way to
look at it. Um, but thank
[clears throat] you for sharing that. Go
ahead.
>> Yeah. So, now what I want this isn't a
conversation about jobs. I think Martin
already did that uh earlier this week,
so we don't need to have that
conversation. Let's go back to the
everything bull market. So, in a time
when macro looks really good, right? The
question is, okay, well, where do you
invest? And obviously, if I think that
AI is the thing that's that's really
helping the macro economy, we got to
understand is AI going to continue,
right? A lot of people and every time I
post on Twitter, I get a bunch of people
saying, look, this thing's a bubble. Um
there's no ROI. The frontier models are
cooked. uh the companies that are
integrating AI are cooked um and it's
too costly for them blah blah blah blah
and the reason why I call this the
everything bull market particular to
those using and involved in AI is
because if you really look at the
numbers if you look at across the stack
of AI meaning the infrastructure layer
the model layer and the application
layer every single layer is ROI positive
they are all seeing a return on their
investment and when that happens it
means you can continue to scale fail
this. It means it's not going to stop.
If a company can spend money on Open AI
and Enthropic and make money, they're
just going to continue to do that,
right? And if Enthropic and Open AAI can
spend money on compute, whether it's
from a Neocloud or SpaceX or from Google
or whoever, and they can make money off
of it, they're going to continue to do
that. And of course, if these neoclouds
and these cloud companies and these
compute companies and the memory
companies can make more money uh selling
their products, they're going to keep,
you know, building and manufacturing
those products. Okay. So, if we look at
the entire layer, here's a chart that's
up right now that shows um that this is
looking at 117 companies. They make more
than 500 u million dollars a year in
revenues.
And for companies that that spend money
on tokens, they make three times more
than those that are not. And their
revenues are growing the more that they
spend on tokens. Meaning the more money
they give to OpenAI and Enthropic, the
more revenues that they make. And when
you compare it to those that are not
spending money on OpenAI Enthropic, you
see that those that are spending the
money are making three times more.
They're growing three times faster than
those that are not spending. So we can
see the application layer is making
money. This is the like Palunteer
stories, the Service Now stories. So
those companies sure are making money,
but what they're doing is they're
helping companies integrate AI within
their companies and they are making more
money. The more they integrate AI, you
see it again with our company, right,
with Milk Road, with Impact 3, have an
agency. The more that we can use AI, the
more that we are generating additional
revenue and better earnings as a result.
And this is happening across many many
many companies across the stock market
and just in general across the US. So
that's the application layer. This could
be Eli Liy in biotech that's using AI.
This could be SAS companies that's using
AI like Salesforce and Service Now and
you know whoever else, right? This could
be just your average company like um you
know a Robin Hood or a Coinbase who have
talked a lot about using AI and they're
getting way more. They can ship way
faster. their their their earnings are
getting better as a result of it. Um so
there's many different subtypes of
companies that fit within this. Okay. So
the application layer is making more the
more they use AI. So that's key. Okay.
That's the first thing to understand.
Now we got to go to the model layer.
This was a chart that came out from semi
analysis I think last week and they said
that for every gigawatt that open AAI or
Enthropic buys they can make a hundred
billion dollars off of it through
inference API inference API just means
companies using their product to chat
with it to build agents with it etc
$und00 billion so you've heard the
number of Elon Musk saying that they can
sell a gigawatt of compute for 30 to50
billion ion dollar a year. Well, the
reason they can do that is because
Enthropic and Open AI can make a h
100red billion a year. So, if they sell
it for 50 billion, Enthropic and Open AI
make 2x that. If they sell it for 30
billion, Enthropic and Open AI make more
than 3x that. Some of the neoclouds have
been selling long-term deals for 10
billion a year, which means they can
make 10x that. So, do you think
Enthropic and Open Air are going to
continue to spend more or less on
compute? they're going to spend a
ton more because they can make way more
money when they do it. Okay. So, do you
think the capex continues? Does Google
and Amazon and SpaceX and Nibius and
Cororeweave have the capital that they
need to keep buying more to build out
these data centers and buy these GPUs
etc. Well, the answer is yes because
companies like OpenAI, Enthropic, you
also got to include Microsoft in there.
They can do the same thing here. You
also now can probably start to include
SpaceX. Grock and Cursor is becoming a
very legit um uh frontier model. I think
they're going to start to eat market
share on Enthropic and Open AI with
their new launch of 4.6 Grock and their
Grockbot. So, I think you're going to
have a fourth player and you could maybe
say Gemini as well, but I don't know
that they're making this kind of money,
but I think you're going to see that
with SpaceX. Um and so we have four
model companies uh that are able to
spend this much money on on on uh
compute and they can make uh a return on
it. So that is a huge number. And then
lastly, we just had a report come out um
earlier this week that Enthropic um
there's two numbers to look at here.
First, Enthropic has reached a $65
billion annualized revenue run rate.
Open air has reached 40 billion which is
huge. Okay, so they are now making
between the two of them hundred billion
dollars in run rate a year and it is
growing extremely fast. How fast? Well,
in Q2, Enthropic made 11.5 billion.
That's up 14x year overyear. 14 freaking
X, which is absolutely insane numbers.
In Q1, they were at 4.7 billion. So,
they more than doubled that quarter over
quarter. They almost 2xed it quarter
over quarter or sorry, 3xed it quarter
over quarter. So, and then and then if
you look at OpenAI, so Enthropic is not
even the fastest growing now. So, those
numbers are insane. Open AAI more than
doubled their codeex users in one month.
From July 12th to August 12th, they went
from 6 million users to 15 million
users.
>> Oh my god. So, they more than doubled I
think they they doubled their revenue in
the last two months or something like
that. I forget what it was. Um, so
they're growing faster. And then I think
cursor and anthropic or sorry cursor and
grock are doing a similar thing but from
a much smaller base. They're at like
maybe I we don't know but let's say like
6 to 8 billion revenue run rate right
now. Um I think they're going to hit 10
to 20 billion at least by the end of
this year. Um and the expectations
is Enthropic and um Enthropic supposed
to reach 100 to 120 billion by the end
of this year revenue run rate. uh Open
AI, we don't know, but let's say they
can maybe double uh maybe even less than
that, but let's say somewhere between 60
and 80 billion. So, their their run rate
by the end of this year is is 200
billion, just those two companies. And
if you were listening to the All-In
podcast on Friday, Gavin Baker and I
think it was David Saxs, maybe I forget,
we're talking about where they expect it
to go by the end of next year, and
they're expecting Enthropic to reach
somewhere between 250 billion to 400
billion.
which is like insane numbers, especially
when you consider that everyone thought
that the models were going to get
crushed by open uh by the open source
models and they're not. They're
continuing to grow. So, we're seeing
every layer of the stack has an ROI
positive and that tells you that this
can continue for longer than most people
think. You know, one thing we've talked
about a lot on this show is that crypto
is quickly becoming a huge part of the
global payments infrastructure and
nowhere is that more obvious than in
Asia. But if you're actually running a
remittance company or a payment
business, you know that the hard part
isn't moving. the stable coins. It's
dealing with local banking partners,
compliance, liquidity, and all of the
operational headaches that come with
sending money into places like India and
Southeast Asia. That's why today's
partner is Saber. They give payment
companies stable coinpowered
infrastructure to collect and make
payouts across Asia without having to
build all of that complexity themselves.
They've already processed more than $3
billion in transactions across 40
different countries. So, this isn't just
a concept. These guys are actually doing
this for real. If you're building
payment infrastructure or expanding into
Asia, make sure you check out
saber.money. My god, man. I hadn't seen
these numbers. So, I think that I think
that this is what people like your
family and stuff like that, like they
don't understand is the revenue growth
of these companies even in recent times,
right? Like that's the thing. I think a
lot of people think like, well, this is
so overblown, it's so overhyped, it's a
bubble, whatever. Just talk about the
common narrative. But it's it's clear
that when you actually look at the
numbers, the money they're reporting,
it's obscene and it's going to continue
to grow. And for everything from what
I've learned doing these shows with you
guys, it's like all these companies like
like they are projecting for that
growth. And also on the application
side, it's like they're using it like a
lot of big companies are using it. Eli
Liy is a really great example. We keep
coming back to that that both you and
Vincent have talked about that company u
tons. It's the biggest biotech company
in the world are releasing the S&P 500
and over a trillion dollar market cap
and that they are actively showing
revenue from using AI, right? And that's
going to trickle down, inspire everybody
else. Um, and there's that demand for
that is just going to continue to grow
and they're going to want to keep using
it and hire people all the way back to
jobs that use it. Right. Exactly. Now,
look, at some point we will reach a top
here. Uh, at some point the revenues of
Open AI Enthropic will likely start to
decelerate. Uh, maybe flatline. Um, and
that will become likely problematic.
Maybe the thing is is like I don't know
when that happens because the other
thing to think about actually I don't
have this chart prepared but I can find
it pretty quickly. Um I was showing this
on my live show yesterday. If you want
to pull up my screen again. Yeah I got
it right here. This chart here. So if we
look at right now most of us use chat.
Okay. So we just talk to entropic and
open AI. What's coming here and where
the the real demand really comes from is
from agents both enterprise agents and
consumer agents. Enterprise agents has
just started this year. Consumer agents
has not started. Um but it's about to
kick off end of this year. Um and enter
for through Apple and and Google. Um and
then enterprise agents has already
started and the TAM for that is just
absolutely massive. And then you have
from that physical AI which is our
robotics. And so there just keeps being
waves of more and more demand that
continue to kick off and they keep like
um transitioning on top of each other.
It's not like we've got to wait a few
years and then all of a sudden it kicks
in like with the internet, right? It's
like we overbuilt uh we had to wait uh
until we had enough fiber that we could
get like video, right? Then all of a
sudden, okay, that was the next big
demand and then we had to wait for like
mobile to come. But that's not happening
here because these things are happening
so fast. So it's like chat, then we have
agents. The one that there might be a
gap maybe is between agents like digital
agents uh and then uh and physical AI.
But the thing is I think that agents
have so much room to grow that it just
means there's so much more demand for
these tokens. And the thing is the
reason why I think the um open source
models have not cut into the share I
mean they have cut into the share a
little bit of entropic open but the
reason why these companies can continue
to grow is because they don't have the
UI and UX for a company to come in and
distribute AI to thousands of employees
and allow them to you know build agents
and connect into their software and
their CRM and all this kind of stuff and
have control over their usage and the
costs etc. Entropic and OpenAI have
built that that sort of like
administrative layer and all the tools
to connect and do all that kind of
stuff. If I want to go use like Kim K3
or DeepSeek, I've got to go build that
myself. Now, most companies aren't going
to do that. Some will, but most aren't,
which is why most companies are still
continuing to onboard into Codeex and
into Enthropic um and use that. And so I
think we've still got a long ways and
and the more that we we use that and the
more they have this kind of like um this
head start the more that it's hard to
move off because everything is now
integrated into your your enthropic or
into your open AI platform. So um they
continue to hold that and continue to
grow as a result of that and they keep
launching new you know new things like
agents within that. So, um I just think
at some point this will slow down and it
will matter, but right now when you have
a Goldilocks macro moment and you still
have significantly increasing demand,
you've got to be investing in this stuff
during that time point. Again, this will
stop at some point and maybe it's next
year. I don't know when, but right now
it's not that moment.
>> Kyle, how are you expressing all this in
your portfolio?
>> Yeah. So, first I just want to show this
chart here which is around timing. So um
and then because this matters this
matters of when you express this in
terms of your portfolio. So this is an
interesting chart on just looking at
investor sentiment right so just because
the macro is really good and the
earnings are really good and everyone's
adopting AI doesn't mean that
everything's just going to always go up
right again as I said at the beginning
of the show we do have pullbacks. So
there are you you want to try to time
when you enter into different companies
or just into the broader market. So this
is an interesting chart that shows um
you know if you were paying attention to
this earlier this year then you saw that
all this was true you know good macro
setup uh you know AI buildout is crazy
capback's going to continue blah blah
blah and we had at the same time we had
a trade war that happened so again
similar to what I did during the the
pullback that we just had in July if you
were paying attention to these numbers
and everything and saw what was
happening you would have saw that this
was an amazing time to be buying because
the market sold off like crazy during
the beginning of the Iran war. Okay.
Then it ripped and got a little bit
crazy, right, back in like May. And so
maybe what that point when investor
sentiment was so greedy and everyone was
allocated and it was absolutely crazy
and Micron was going nuts and whatever,
that's probably not the time you want to
be buying. What you want to do again is
wait for fear. And so we had that happen
again in July. So long as the macro
backdrop looked good and everything I'm
talking about on the AI side looks good,
that's your time to deploy at scale,
right? You want to put a lot of money
into the market if you can. If you were
a Milkward Pro member, we had tons of
calls over that like few weeks there in
July. Actually, in both of these in
February, March, we were we were calling
to buy a bunch of assets during this
time. We we bought the bottom a bunch.
Um and then same again here in back in
July. Milker Pro members got a bunch of
calls to buy Micron, to buy Nibius, to
buy Coroweavee, to buy I don't remember
what else, but a bunch of things over
those few weeks because the riskreward
was so good in that moment. Right now,
if you look at today in August, you
know, we've had a pretty sharp uh uh
jump back from that pullback. Um and so
investor sentiment is now very bullish.
They are very excited. Again, we've hit
all-time highs in the stock market, and
the S&P um doesn't mean it's not a good
time to buy. you know, Nibbius, Micron,
and a bunch of these other assets still
have not hit all-time highs. So, I think
we are still going to run further here.
But I just want people to realize is
that you want to have this data that I'm
talking about and then you want to
really deploy when there's fear, which
is a very hard thing to do. And I think
one of the best things you can do is
have a group of people or analysts that
can help you get through that. That's
why we launched Milk Road Pro. Milk Road
Pro, just so you guys know, is uh a
place where five analysts, really top
tier analysts, share their research like
this. Um, and they share their real-time
portfolios and live trades and their
research. And it basically puts, you
know, for you guys that are just
consumers and maybe not working
full-time checking out the markets. It
puts the bull market on easy mode for
you because you don't have to figure all
this out. You literally just get a
message in your email saying, "Hey,
we're buying this at this time now. We
think it's a good time to buy." Blah
blah blah blah. So, um, if you are not
yet a pro member, go do it because it
puts the bull market on easy mode for
you. You can make a lot of money doing
this. Uh, and we're going to help you do
that. So, that's the the key thing is
around timing. Um, and then the next
thing is where do you invest your
capital? And I think there's there's
three layers to think about it, right?
And I actually think you probably want
to invest across all three. The first
layer is the infrastructure side. So, we
talk about a ton of that on this show.
That's your memory and GPUs and semis
and um, and you know, compute and uh,
power and so on.
So you can look to buy assets there. And
I think as long as capex continues to
grow, you want to have a basket of those
assets. You don't just want to own one,
you want to own a basket of those
assets. The application layer is the
other area where I think is really good,
which is look at good companies that are
integrating AI and as a result their
earnings are going to improve. Um, and I
think that's a really good spot to be
investing in. You mentioned Eli Liy.
That is a big part of of my portfolio.
Um, I've talked a lot about SAS.
Whenever I tweet about SAS, no one likes
it, but that's because it's down like
50%. Um, however, we were buying it uh
at its very bottom and it's it's done
very well. It's outperformed a lot of
the infrastructure side. I think owning
both of those almost like a barbell is
really good. Now, the model layer you
could own, but the problem is it's all
private, so you can't really own it
right now outside of uh Cursor and Grock
inside of SpaceX, but I think that the
price of that company is um being priced
very different than, you know, just a
pure play uh frontier model. So, I
really like the barbell strategy, which
is own the software um and the
application layer side and then own the
infrastructure side. Kyle, can you um
talk about this fear, this kind of
investor sentiment chart uh and these
huge dips being opportunities? We got
one comment yesterday during your live
stream from a guy saying that and this
is a lot of people get into Milk Road
Pro and they're you know again they got
we got Nebius calls way back uh in like
February at $300 which is fant or Micron
even or or AMD all these companies that
have ripped but even on the short term
for getting these like notifications of
buying these dips what did this guy say
he made 60k he made 60k in the last week
and I'm assuming this is from yeah
exactly all these calls SpaceX Sandis uh
Nebius Did we call Santa? I don't even
know if that's true, [laughter] but it's
one of the companies that bounced back,
but definitely in that dip in the last
couple weeks, especially through July,
you guys were buying. Melvin was buying,
man. Plowing back into those Neocloud,
saying he's super bullish and that this
is an amazing buying opportunity. Nebas
went all the way down to like 147
yesterday. It was at like 280 or
something. Literally a 2x opportunity.
So, this guy making some cash from that.
>> Well, here's the thing. You either get
the calls from us or you at least get
the research that gives you kind of the
layout to understand the market and then
you can make your own investments too.
You might buy things that we don't hold,
but it fits the thesis, right? There's a
lot of things you can buy on the barbell
strategy I just talked about. And I own
a bunch of assets within them. So does
Melvin. So does Martin. So do all of our
analysts, but you might buy others as
well. Um, and yeah, this guy here who
was in my live stream yesterday made 60K
just last week because of the Milk Road
Pro calls. Now, here's the thing, guys.
It's $25 a month, okay? And this guy
made 60K in a freaking week. That ROI is
better than any ROI you've ever seen. I
don't care. You can try to use AI to
build a company. You're not getting an
ROI that good. No way. Here's the thing,
though. We are running a campaign right
now because Milk Road Pro is getting so
freaking good that we're actually
increasing the prices by a lot. So, what
was once $25 a month, it's moving to uh
$39 a month. What was once 25 $250 a
year is moving to $299 a year. But this
week you can get it at the same price at
this $25 a month or $250 a year, which I
would recommend the yearly cuz it's way
cheaper. Um for the next week, you can
lock in that price and you get it for
life. So if you if you sign up to Milk
Road Pro this week, you get that price
for life even though we're going to
close to double the cost at least on the
monthly basis. And here's the thing, the
reason we are increasing the prices is
because Milk Road Pro has changed a ton.
So, we used to be just one portfolio,
now we have five portfolios, five
analysts. We are launching a portfolio
tracker in the next few weeks here,
which means you can connect your
accounts. You can see your exact
portfolio, line it up along with all of
our analyst portfolios. You're also
about to get um uh professional
investors portfolios that you can see.
So Gavin Baker and others like that,
you're going to see them inside and
you're going to see them all across who
owns the same assets that you own, how
much do they own, how does it fit in
their portfolio, um and you're going to
be able to get a bunch of analysis based
on our analysts um on your own
portfolio. So this is going to be really
really cool and um we're super super
excited about this. This is coming at
the end of August, probably early
September. Uh and so that's why the
prices are actually raising because this
is going to get even better. By the way,
there's also a community where you can
sit there and you can talk to me and the
four other analysts any time in the day
and ask us any questions about your
portfolio. So, it's just uh yeah, it's
crazy to do this bull market alone and
not do it with Milk Road Pro.
>> And you know, and I think another thing
too, Kyle, just to point out about Milk
Road Pro and and it is a good time for
an increase because people are getting
value. That's a 25,000% return. Uh that
guy, you know, being subscribed for 20
$25 a month and being able to make a
trade that made him 60k. Um, I think
it's also important to talk about how
much that that the product has evolved
dramatically. Even in my time in Milk
Road, man, like this is, you know, the
amount of stuff that we have now is
obscene. We have real time notifications
for trades. Like, how awesome is that,
man? It's not just, you know, you would
have gotten the notifications last week
or whenever wasn't that someone like
Melvin who has been our Neocloud
champion, he's plowing back in during
that dip. And those days where you have
that extreme fear, you're scared, you're
like, maybe maybe I missed, maybe I
missed it, you know, maybe I should have
gotten out. um you know you'd have that
signal from us to continue to get into
the market and everything else is going
to continue to happen from here. Kyle,
>> you also have I talked you know the
first 20 minutes of this show uh about
uh macro. We have a Milk Road macro
index which basically gives you a
barometer on macro at all times. You
literally can see it every single day.
And every week there's an update from
one of our analysts John uh giving you a
breakdown of the macro environment and
what it means. Should you be buying?
Should you not be buying? And you can
see we are very risk on right now, which
tells you exactly what I was saying. Um,
so just as a quick look here. Oh, look
at there's been a couple buys today. I
got to get out of that. So, everyone
here can't see. You got to pay to to
[laughter] see that, but looks like
there was some buys. Um, but here's some
updates on Nibius this morning. Uh, I
made a buy some SpaceX. Uh, here's your
MRMI brief. Uh, we do earnings updates.
So, every time there's an earnings, any
of the companies that we hold, um, we do
updates on them. Uh and uh yeah, it's um
there's just there's a lot that you are
gonna get here to turn this bull market
on easy mode.
>> Exactly. And to just and to just keep up
and I think is also we have different
analysts and you guys cross over
theme-wise but you also have your
different strategies. You also have your
different ways of doing it and I think
that that's really helpful for people
and even all the features that are
coming uh you know totally worth the
price and and justified for the for for
the price increase because this stuff is
really good man. So, this is your last
week, guys, to get in at this price.
Price goes up 60% on the monthly. That's
the calculation, Kyle. So, that's that's
a big increase. So, if you want to get
in at that $25 a month, this is your
chance now. The next couple days, uh, is
is basically the the last time that you
can do it. So, the link is below.
>> Let me just say Q4 is going to be very
bullish. You're going to want to be in
the market. You're going to want to know
what stocks to be buying because, as I
just showed you, we're in a Goldilocks
moment in macro. We are in an incredible
opportunity in terms of AI as I just
talked about. That's not stopping this
year. That might stop next year and we
will of course let you guys know when we
think that's going to happen, but I
think we have another big leg to go in
the market and uh and so you want to be
involved in that. So you can try to
invest alone if you'd like. Um but why
not do it with friends?
>> That's and that's what we do in Milk
Road Pro. Kyle, it's been a great
episode, man. Thank you for sharing your
theory on the everything bull market.
And again, if you guys want to go pro,
now's the time. Uh, it's at the link
below and all the information is there.
Make sure you sign up and if you got any
questions about today's episode, sign up
and go ask Kyle in our Discord. Go grill
him or write a a question on one of his
pro updates. You can do both of those to
get in touch with him. Otherwise, Kyle,
good to see you, man. Thank you for all
the info.
>> Thank you everyone. Thanks for listening
to Milk Road. If you enjoyed the show,
make sure you like and subscribe.
[music] And if you're struggling to find
winners in the market, that's exactly
what Milkro Pro is built for. Our
analysts [music] have called some of the
biggest winners early, and Pro lets you
see what they're buying next. every
trade they make and the research behind
every position. Check out Milk Road Pro
at the link below. Everything you hear
on Milkroad is forformational purposes
only. These are our personal opinions,
not financial advice, and we may own
some of the investments we talk about.
Always do your own research and make the
[clears throat] decisions that are right
for you. See you next time.